Guide to the John A. Nietz Papers UA.90.F95
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Artifacts, IX.
  - Hammond Gazette (Point Lookout, MD) 1:42, September 1, 1863 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Clippings, Religious Education and McGuffy Readers (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Feria Quinta, Feria Sextus, 1551? (Box 16, Folder 19-19a)
  - Old School Books Exhibit Boards (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Education in Great Britain Exhibit Placards (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - A Short Introduction to Grammer Plackard (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Bricks from Samuel Reed Hall's Normal School in Concord Vermont, 1823 (Box 17, Item 1)
  - Joseph Ray's Writing Slate, 1788 (Box 17, Item 2)
  - Writing Slate (20x29 cm) (Box 17, Item 3)
  - Horn Book in Case (Box 17, Item 4)
  - St. Paul's Hornbook, 1729 (Box 17, Item 5)
  - Early School Bell (Box 17, Item 6)
  - Countertop Bell (Box 17, Item 7)
  - Sierra Leone Kissi (pennies) (Box 17, Item 8)
  - McGuffy Reader Ceramic Ornament (Box 17, Item 9)
  - Samuel Pepys Faux Book (Box 17, Item 10)